







DEV LANGUAGES

JavaScript, jQuery

Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Adobe Creative Cloud

PHP, Python, R, InVision, Justinmind MySQL, Java, C++

I'm a **UI/UX Designer** with 3+ years of experience designing simple & enriching digital solutions. My passion lies in bridging the gap between Innovative Technology and Social Impact through the power of Design.



EXPERIENCE

### **UX Design Intern**

GE Energy Connections, Redmond, WA | June 2016 - Present

- Currently working on redesigning e-terrasimulator Dispatcher Training Simulator a software training system used by electrical power grid operators.
- Based on a corporate-wide initiative to transform legacy software into new versions that more closely align with modern usability & interface design standards, the project entails the creation & design of new features & functionality as well as overall user experience improvements.

## **UI/UX Designer**

Joomla, Seattle, WA | July 2015 - March 2016

- Worked with various volunteers around the world on a redesign (usability & interface) project for the next web versions of Joomla CMS, Joomla 3.5 (release in March 2016), as part of the product development roadmap.
- Participated in various web & mobile redesign projects for Joomla.com Joomla's primary websites as part of an initiative to improve user sign up rates as well as branding.

#### **UI/UX Designer**

Pinky Swear App, Seattle, WA | March 2015 – March 2016

- Collaborated with a developer to design & build Pinky Swear an Android mobile application that wants to reimagine the productivity space by allowing users to make promises with matched users and communicate with them via a chat messenger.
- Drove the end-to-end design process for **two releases (500+ downloads)** of the application, from user/market research, ideation, prototyping, to final design production.

#### **UI/UX Designer**

**VnExpress, Seattle (Remote), WA | September 2013 – June 2015** 

- Helped design & build the VnExpress Mobile App (release in September 2014) the official mobile channel (iOS & Android) for VnExpress, one of the most popular online news outlets in Vietnam.
- Lead the complete design initiative for VnExpress International the English version of the website from concept development to high-fidelity design proposals for development team.



EDUCATION

# **MS in Information Management** (User Experience Research & Design)

University of Washington, Seattle | September 2015 – Present

**BA in International Studies** (International Political Economy & Business)

University of Washington, Seattle | September 2012 – June 2014